Theme Tune:
Kevin: Hello, farmers, and welcome once again to another episode of The Harvest Season.
Kevin: My name is Kevin, and we are here today to talk about Cottagecore games!
Chelsea: And my name is Chelsea.
Chelsea: Oh, yeah.
Kevin: Woo!
Kevin: Yeah, hello everyone. We're slipping back into the time stream.
Kevin: Bug month has formally concluded, as it were for now.
Kevin: So, good to...
Kevin: Yeah, I'm very excited. I see what we'll have...
Kevin: I wonder what we'll have to do.
Kevin: Good run on bug month. Good job, Codey.
Kevin: Actually, you know what? Shout out.
Kevin: How appropriate, right as she finished up bug month.
Kevin: Codey also...
Chelsea: - Yes, congratulations, Dr. Mathis.
Kevin: Yep, officially graduated.
Kevin: Yeah, I've been calling her Dr. Mathis for a while. I don't know.
Kevin: But by the way, she's officially Professor Dr. Codey Mathis.
Kevin: authority on the bug
Chelsea: We are so proud of you.
Kevin: yeah um and so yeah well yeah so I guess
Chelsea: Yes, bug authorities.
Kevin: what a what an appropriate way to end
Kevin: bug month um yeah you got great
Kevin: episodes I still haven't finished last
Kevin: week's episode it's it's the last two
Chelsea: It's hefty.
Kevin: episodes were meaty um yeah but uh but
Chelsea: We be yappin'.
Kevin: as we will do this episode because now we
Chelsea: Woo!
Kevin: have to catch up with everything we
Kevin: skipped over the last month
Kevin: Woo!
Kevin: Um, yes, okay, but before that, you know, as we do, we'll talk about other stuff.
Kevin: Well, actually, no, Chelsea, what have you been up to?
Kevin: Ignore me.
Chelsea: I'll keep it short. Okay, so I started. Okay, I'll donate my time to you. Okay, so I started a book called Dungeon Crawler Carl that so many people have recommended to me and I'm five or six chapters in and absolutely hooked. Have you heard about this book?
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: Don't, I won't.
Kevin: Ha, ha, ha.
Kevin: I have heard of it I i've heard uh how should I put this wild things about this book
Chelsea: yeah so yeah I'm only six chapters in and um I had borrowed the book and I also have the audible
Chelsea: version and what oh my god the narration is hilarious um yeah I've been doing it while I
Kevin: No, the audibles. This sounds like a good one for audible.
Chelsea: I craft um I've been I've been doing this bedazzled goose lamp I'll show photos once it's done it
Kevin: Oh, that one's good.
Chelsea: sounds really dumb but it's no it's fun I'm enjoying it um aside from that yeah that's oh
Kevin: Uh-oh, that's one for this.
Chelsea: and then yesterday my husband and I went to spirit Halloween it is never I don't care it's never too
Kevin: Yeah.
Chelsea: early it's there it's in an abandoned Toys R Us it's kind of sad has the shell like if you go behind
Kevin: Yeah, yeah, the logos, yeah.
Chelsea: the curtain they still have all the like the displays and stuff and yeah I kind of want to
Chelsea: just buy one see if I can get like a what's his name Jeff the giraffe or Jerry the giraffe see if
Kevin: yeah jeffrey jeffrey but anyways um they should just lean into it
Chelsea: I can get a stand of his
Chelsea: Jeffrey
Chelsea: they should that would be amazing
Kevin: they should have put up a jeffrey in a reaper cloak but uh
Chelsea: anyway so we still have one Toys R Us
Chelsea: left in the city
Chelsea: but I think it's closing pretty soon
Chelsea: I know I know
Kevin: Oh, it's really just dead.
Chelsea: it's the one thing for Canada we have Toys R Us
Chelsea: but it got it went bankrupt
Chelsea: I don't know if it went bankrupt or someone else bought it out
Kevin: This may be an impossible question to answer,
Chelsea: but like it's not it's nothing anymore
Kevin: but you as a parent,
Kevin: you are probably better equipped to answer this.
Kevin: Do you think there is need for toy stores?
Chelsea: Yes.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: I just want to make sure.
Kevin: I thought there were,
Kevin: and I know it's a bunch of corporate
Chelsea: Yeah.
Kevin: nonsense that led to Toys R Us
Kevin: dying, but
Kevin: I still feel like that is a demand
Kevin: that exists. I just want it to be.
Chelsea: Yeah. And there's still, I don't know if it's in the States too, but in Canada, we have Mastermind
Chelsea: Toys. And they were like the more chic Toys R Us, I guess. They're still around. They're doing
Chelsea: pretty well. But they're obviously filling in the market that Toys R Us left behind around here.
Kevin: Yeah, sadly.
Chelsea: I don't know if my nostalgia is blinding me, but I love, even as a grown-up, taking the kids to
Chelsea: Toys R Us. I'm like, yes, we can go to Toys R Us. Yeah, we're going to look at those overpriced
Kevin: Oh, yes.
Kevin: No.
Chelsea: everything.
Kevin: Yeah, yeah.
Chelsea: But no, it was, yeah, no, I think
Chelsea: there still would be a place for Toys R Us.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: Yeah, I think so, too.
Kevin: Obviously, as anyone who's listened to this show can tell you,
Kevin: I'm still just a big kid.
Kevin: So I dig it.
Kevin: I haven't been to Toys R Us in years.
Kevin: It's not existing down here.
Kevin: But, yeah, sadly, we don't have any replacements.
Kevin: It's just pretty much the big box retailers.
Kevin: Technically, the branding was used in, I think, Macy's.
Kevin: There's, like, a toy section there, but it's, you know,
Kevin: it's Macy's still, so whatever.
Chelsea: Oh, yeah, we tried that in Canada. Not with Toys R Us, but we had Zellers, which if anyone knows what that is, it's like Canadian Walmart, basically. They close. That's a whole, we don't have time to get into Canadian Tire.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Mm-hmm.
Kevin: I don't know.
Kevin: I'm looking it up.
Kevin: Oh, okay.
Kevin: I thought that was Canadian Tire.
Kevin: I found one near me the other day.
Chelsea: That's a whole episode on its own. Like, do a video tour of Canadian Tire and say, like, live tour of what's going on in the store. Anyway, so yeah.
Chelsea: So Zellers was basically Canadian Walmart. And then they tried to do a rebrand and have part of Hudson's Bay Company, which ironically was purchased by Canadian Tire.
Kevin: Ha ha ha ha ha!
Chelsea: But they had a section of Hudson's Bay Company as like a little pop-up Zellers. But I don't know how well that worked, but apparently they're bringing Zellers back. But then at the same time, yeah, Canadian Tire.
Kevin: Uh-huh.
Chelsea: Canadian Tire bought Hudson's Bay. So it's just a bunch of companies in a top hat. Like, it's all just one thing. So it doesn't even matter. But yeah, Canadian Tire. Oh my god, Kevin, if you come to Canada, that's the first place I'm bringing you.
Kevin: that's funny
Kevin: yeah
Kevin: what if I told you I found one near me oh yeah it's about so it's uh yeah let me look up things
Chelsea: No.
Kevin: I believe it's for red um anyways it's in one of these atlanta suburbs um it's very funny how i
Kevin: found it um it was my sister's birthday recently and I was looking for some stuff and I looked for
Kevin: a specific uh anime store because she's a huge weeb too anyway so I drove down there was about
Kevin: 25 minutes from where I am
Kevin: and lo and behold I see the sign
Kevin: for a Canadian
Kevin: tire right there
Kevin: I didn't go to it sadly didn't have time
Kevin: but it exists
Kevin: in the area I'll have to see what it's like
Kevin: and we'll have to compare notes
Kevin: the US
Kevin: you know knockoff
Chelsea: i'm looking it up and it says I don't know I don't okay it says there's no canadian
Chelsea: tire retail stores located in the united states I don't know i
Chelsea: that's a lie what would ai just lie to me
Kevin: that's a lie I i i'm i'm looking it up let's hold on hold on hold on let's live on camera it is uh
Chelsea: okay it says things like farm and fleet are comparable
Kevin: um wait oh my gosh I think I was duped was I duped no I think it was just
Chelsea: Did someone just, like, ah, oh, my goodness, Kevin.
Kevin: it's just canada tire company wow okay
Kevin: wow okay what a ride um anyways I will say this I don't know anything about zellers but uh
Kevin: i'm down for any store that has uh zetti the as their mascot
Kevin: they had a restaurant too wow this is
Chelsea: I love Zeddy.
Chelsea: Yeah, there used to be this little Ferris wheel ride in the store.
Chelsea: Oh, the restaurant was incredible.
Kevin: yeah no yes
Chelsea: This is how we're starting this episode?
Chelsea: No, it was like this like 50s diner.
Chelsea: They had amazing milkshakes.
Chelsea: There was one in the mall.
Chelsea: There used to be a big Zeller's at a mall that was near my house
Chelsea: that I actually worked at for a little bit.
Chelsea: And then they went bankrupt.
Chelsea: Not because of me, though.
Chelsea: I promise.
Chelsea: No, but they had an amazing like 50s diner with like grilled cheese
Chelsea: and all these diner staple
Chelsea: it was so
Chelsea: it had no business
Chelsea: being that good
Chelsea: for what it was
Kevin: oh that sounds oh walmart's got nothing on those how did you people
Chelsea: nothing
Chelsea: well
Kevin: how did you canadians let zellers die
Kevin: yeah yeah I remember that yeah
Chelsea: then we tried to have Target
Chelsea: and that lasted
Chelsea: like maybe two years
Chelsea: yeah
Kevin: yeah yeah actually you know it's funny like I get why a failure but I like target it's
Chelsea: that was a
Chelsea: that was a bummer
Chelsea: I liked it
Kevin: probably one of the uh better national brands I would say but uh anyway
Chelsea: mm-hmm we have a long enough episode as it is
Kevin: okay that's exciting oh yeah no let's say that for the greenhouse review national
Chelsea: yeah I need the entire tour what have you been up to kevin
Kevin: um okay um it's been a minute since i've been on so and I have done stuff shockingly
Kevin: um okay you talked about brand new day I watched the brand new day um i'm just gonna say well
Chelsea: yes thumbs up
Kevin: thumbs up i'm not gonna go into details um i'll give you guys about a minute i'm gonna give an
Kevin: anti-spoiler just my big complaint was something that was not in the movie um well i'll say a
Chelsea: Okay.
Kevin: minute I do whatever like 10 seconds 15 seconds whatever um close your ears children you don't
Kevin: the cowards didn't do man spider um chelsea you don't understand how much
Kevin: I love man spider it's the stupidest thing in comics and that's why it's my absolute favorite
Kevin: and they I thought they were gonna do it and they didn't um there's a yeah like the
Kevin: okay i'm not gonna get too deep into it because there's there's a whole history behind that
Chelsea: I didn't have the hotspot to do it.
Kevin: deep marvel head but i'm sad they didn't do it but anyways uh good job yeah good job um so yeah
Chelsea: Greenhouse time.
Kevin: all right brand new day that was good
Chelsea: Did you have a PSP playing group of teenagers beside you?
Kevin: no actually about that okay i'm not the talkative one but first of all the theater wasn't too
Kevin: uh full uh full when we went it was like 10 p.m on like a wednesday night or something uh 8 p.m
Kevin: whatever um so it wasn't that full but and uh there was nobody like in our row um but my sister be
Kevin: we went for her birthday basically and uh uh it was uh she's a big web head too um so uh I was the one
Kevin: we were whispering back and forth not being disruptive but uh but uh we we there were murmurs
Kevin: here and there mostly me being excited and and and poking her to let her know I was excited but uh yeah
Chelsea: Ah, ah, did you see that?
Kevin: Yeah, yeah, yeah, look
Kevin: They're doing the thing
Kevin: Yeah, no, but
Kevin: That was good stuff, Tom Holland
Kevin: Glad you enjoyed the role, because you're probably going to be there
Kevin: For a bit, buddy
Kevin: Yeah, yeah, I don't
Chelsea: Yeah, he must have sent a blood oath or something.
Chelsea: He's there forever.
Chelsea: He's great, though.
Kevin: No one wants to let you go now
Chelsea: I enjoy him.
Kevin: Oh, okay
Chelsea: Nope.
Chelsea: Well, I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Kevin: Yeah, yeah, she did
Chelsea: Your sister enjoyed it, too?
Kevin: Yeah, well, I've said it a handful of times in communications
Kevin: But we need to do an MCU pre-Doomsday episode
Chelsea: - Yes, we do.
Kevin: Because there are many thoughts
Kevin: I am excited for Doomsday, I'll say that
Kevin: But anyways, there's many thoughts
Kevin: Okay, aside from that
Kevin: I have played Pocopia DLC Has Descended Upon the Earth
Kevin: It took me a minute, but I did get into it
Kevin: I have literally dove in
Kevin: As we are now underwater
Kevin: Obviously we're going to do an episode
Kevin: On it so I won't get into too much detail
Kevin: I'm of course enjoying it
Kevin: The one thing I will say
Kevin: That is pretty cool
Kevin: Just on a general level
Kevin: Having a new area
Kevin: But having all your tools
Kevin: Is pretty fun
Kevin: Because you can just start hammering away
Kevin: And building stuff up
Kevin: How you want pretty much immediately
Kevin: Um
Chelsea: Oh, that's good. You don't have to go through a quest to unlock stuff to use in the area.
Kevin: That's great
Kevin: There's a handful of things
Kevin: But I mean
Kevin: Like you see a rundown house
Kevin: You can build up that rundown house right away
Kevin: You know
Kevin: There's a couple of new mechanics and stuff
Kevin: That they do introduce
Kevin: And that's fun
Kevin: But yeah
Kevin: We'll get into detail in the episode
Kevin: But overall I'm loving it
Kevin: I will say
Kevin: Also kudos to them
Kevin: There's a lot of little like
Kevin: Small sneaky quality of life things
Kevin: They added as part of the free update
Kevin: Not the DLC itself
Kevin: Um
Chelsea: Oh, great.
Kevin: Yeah
Kevin: Like trash cans actually work now
Kevin: As trash cans
Kevin: That's a fun little one
Kevin: Um
Kevin: Uh
Kevin: But yeah
Kevin: We'll
Kevin: I'll get into that later
Kevin: But yeah
Kevin: Bubbly basin
Kevin: Good stuff
Kevin: Um
Kevin: Let's see
Kevin: Aside from that
Kevin: Um
Kevin: I have also
Kevin: Uh
Kevin: As we've had too much quality content
Kevin: On the show recently
Kevin: It's time to
Kevin: Talk about some of my
Kevin: Degenerate content
Kevin: Uh
Kevin: I've been
Chelsea: oh dear
Kevin: Uh
Kevin: Getting back into some of my
Kevin: Basically gotchas
Kevin: The first one
Kevin: zone zero uh i've talked about on the show I don't know are you familiar chelsea of zone zero
Chelsea: I don't think so actually
Kevin: okay uh it's hoyo mihoyo the uh genshin impact company um they uh it's one of their big flagship
Chelsea: okay
Kevin: games it's uh it's uh an action sort of game kind of like uh devil may cry but much lighter um
Kevin: yeah so yeah genshin's you know kind of zelda breath of the wild uh the hunkai star rail the
Kevin: space when that's like turn-based
Kevin: RPG this is more
Kevin: fast-paced action combat
Kevin: so that's why it really
Kevin: appealed to me I dove in I've been on it since
Kevin: the beginning and
Kevin: yeah I've been I took a bit of a
Kevin: break with so much work and stuff but
Kevin: jumped back in right around the time they're
Kevin: celebrating their second anniversary
Kevin: and it's
Kevin: yeah they're pretty all the goodies
Kevin: are being handed out it's very fun
Kevin: so yeah I won't go into detail but I will say
Kevin: oh one thing with a lot of these
Kevin: Mojo games pretty much when you start a new
Kevin: it's a new setting
Kevin: it'll be a new quote-unquote season or whatever
Kevin: and it lasts pretty much a year
Kevin: the starting
Kevin: setting was like the city
Kevin: it was very cool I liked it year one
Kevin: or the on the second
Kevin: setting last year's was
Kevin: didn't appeal to me as much I mean it was like
Kevin: kind of rural China
Chelsea: - No.
Kevin: based which I don't know just maybe not the
Kevin: target audience for that but
Kevin: this year we're going into a kind
Kevin: of steampunk
Kevin: floating city in the sky
Kevin: much more like Europe
Kevin: England London
Kevin: a little bit Paris based
Kevin: I find it much more interesting
Kevin: as a setting so I'm enjoying
Kevin: it so far but but yeah
Kevin: yeah anyways
Kevin: I've been doing my pools doing all that good stuff
Kevin: and the other one
Kevin: probably even I can get even more degenerate
Chelsea: Hmm.
Kevin: than Zenless Zone Zero
Kevin: I have been
Kevin: dipping my toe back
Kevin: into the
Kevin: most cursed
Kevin: of all my
Kevin: hobbies
Kevin: yeah it's it's a good time to get back in because
Chelsea: - Yes, yes, I love it.
Kevin: I probably should do a green house on Yu-Gi-Oh at some point
Kevin: but they release and announce sets that they'll often lean into nostalgia and whatnot and so I'll get very excited about some sets and whatnot
Chelsea: Oh my goodness, yes.
Kevin: I'm playing a lot of online right now.
Kevin: The worst part about Yu-Gi-Oh! is there's kind of this, how should I put this, it's very desynced.
Kevin: There's the online version, the actual physical version varies between the Japanese version and the Western version.
Kevin: It's a very strange rollout how they approach it, unlike, say, like Magic the Gathering, which is kind of worldwide all at the same time.
Kevin: But anyways, Yu-Gi-Oh! it's a lot of fun.
Kevin: I'm just picking up games, getting back into it.
Kevin: It's an insane game for...
Kevin: Crazy people, but sadly, I'm stuck here.
Chelsea: oh man don't get me started back in there I did I did but I got to the point where my parents were
Kevin: Have you played Yu-Gi-Oh, Chelsea?
Kevin: I don't understand.
Chelsea: like pick one pokemon digimon yugioh we are not buying stuff for all of these and I said pokemon
Kevin: No. All. Yeah. Oh, 100%. Like right now, they just released a set out in the US. It's called Chaos Impact. I can't remember the name of it. Anyways, it has Yugi on the cover of the packs.
Chelsea: does does yugioh lean into blue eyes the way pokemon leads into charizard
Chelsea: yeah okay okay I kind of figured
Kevin: It's the first time they've done that in like 15, 20 years, whatever, and everyone's losing
Kevin: their minds.
Chelsea: Oh man. Okay. It sounds like a good time to get back in. Like my wallet's jingling.
Kevin: Oh, yeah.
Kevin: It's probably as good as it's going to get.
Chelsea: I love that optimism.
Kevin: The game has inherent problems, but they're releasing fun stuff that appeals to people.
Kevin: I'll say that.
Chelsea: okay so if you get a message from me at 3am like kevin you'll never believe it you have yourself to
Kevin: Oh, you know, if you need me to.
Kevin: But, you know, to be your sharp a little, let me know.
Kevin: But, yeah, Yu-Gi-Oh, I'm dabbling back in.
Kevin: The thing is, I'm never really out.
Kevin: There are just periods where I'm not playing, but I'm never out.
Kevin: I'll be following along.
Kevin: But, yeah, that's good times.
Kevin: Yu-Gi-Oh.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: That's what's been up in my life world.
Kevin: Hello, everyone.
Kevin: Let's just, if you have nothing else, Chelsea, let's dive on into, I know what
Kevin: you released last month-ish, apostrophe, or dash-esque.
Kevin: There's a lot of games that came out.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: June Games.
Kevin: Odd Fauna.
Kevin: The game of your...
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: I didn't realize this.
Kevin: That game has handcrafted clay models.
Chelsea: yes it's super cute I know I watched the trailer just in awe like oh my goodness yes
Kevin: That's insane.
Kevin: So, yeah, I didn't realize that.
Kevin: I'm much more interested in that game.
Kevin: It's, you know, kind of working with creatures and farming on top of the big beast.
Kevin: And they call it the Terror Beast.
Kevin: But the fact that they were handcrafted clay models and then digitized, wow, that's awesome.
Kevin: So, I'm actually intrigued now.
Kevin: Let's see.
Kevin: Solar Punk.
Kevin: That's kind of...
Kevin: It looks like No Man's Sky.
Kevin: It's the farming.
Kevin: You create a base.
Kevin: You use solar and wind energy.
Kevin: I don't have much for this one, guys.
Kevin: You are.
Kevin: Tales of Seikyu?
Kevin: I'm Weeb, but not weeb enough to pronounce Japanese things correctly.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: It's the Yokai Weeb game!
Kevin: So, we all know I'm all in.
Kevin: But also, I didn't realize...
Kevin: I mean, I should have expected, but I didn't realize it.
Kevin: You could date some of these yokais.
Kevin: So, you know, we got our little just hint of furry in there.
Chelsea: Just enough, yeah.
Kevin: But you do.
Kevin: I mean, you are...
Kevin: You're a fox girl, technically.
Kevin: I didn't realize that.
Kevin: But you are a fox yokai.
Kevin: That's why you can transform.
Kevin: All the jokes...
Chelsea: Speaking of fox furries, sorry, I see a beastro up there.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Oh!
Kevin: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kevin: Right it.
Kevin: Ooh, bravo.
Kevin: Yeah, Bistro.
Kevin: You guys know that came out
Kevin: because we talked about it.
Kevin: You talked about it.
Kevin: It's a good episode.
Chelsea: Oh yeah, 100% that game.
Kevin: Ooh, you did.
Chelsea: I did.
Kevin: Ooh, that's sick.
Chelsea: Oh, yeah.
Kevin: That's...
Kevin: I think that's high praise.
Kevin: Anytime we actually go back to finish a game,
Kevin: Cool.
Chelsea: it is I started it
Kevin: July.
Kevin: Moonlight Peaks.
Kevin: That's the game with the vampires.
Kevin: I hear...
Chelsea: oh no no no no no no not spill it anything no no reason no particular reason
Kevin: For any reason, I would wonder.
Kevin: Who knows?
Kevin: Moving on!
Kevin: Oh, you know what?
Kevin: I was about to make a Spirit Halloween joke,
Kevin: but can I go back one second to Spirit Halloween?
Kevin: One thing I saw,
Kevin: they're selling that life-size
Kevin: Five Nights at Freddy's
Kevin: the Fazbear animatronic
Chelsea: oh I have a video of it I sent my kids and they're like mom do not come home with that
Kevin: but what if you did
Chelsea: well then they probably still think we're the coolest house on the block so
Kevin: and I gotta say
Chelsea: I don't have the power source to link that in the front yard like I was thinking about the
Kevin: 500 USD is not bad
Kevin: for like
Kevin: oh what
Chelsea: logistics of it they also had an alien one that was super super cool um yeah yeah I'll post it in
Kevin: wait Alien TM
Kevin: Or...
Chelsea: the Slack. It was super cool.
Chelsea: And I'm like, you know what?
Chelsea: I can't be bringing my wallet in here.
Kevin: that's sick okay so yeah that moonlight peaks the spirit of halloween game uh it's
Kevin: will be talked about on the show maybe um go go town also came out you guys know the one that's
Kevin: on chainsaws and aliens and werewolves and all sorts of nonsense it hit 1.0 good for you go go
Kevin: town I might play you one day you you do look like a good game I will say that um farlands i
Kevin: call it Space Duvalli because it looks like
Kevin: Stardew Valley but it's in
Chelsea: base too. Incredible. Oh, that's all.
Kevin: space and that's all
Kevin: yeah I don't have much else for that
Kevin: I'm sorry
Kevin: The Ranchers came out in
Kevin: July and that's
Kevin: an interesting one
Kevin: yeah yeah because it's quote unquote
Chelsea: I screamed at the trailer when the car just flies up
Chelsea: and the hot air balloon or whatever I was like
Kevin: yeah yeah yeah
Kevin: the hot air balloon
Chelsea: yeah
Kevin: it's quote unquote realistic
Kevin: because that's kind of the aesthetic
Kevin: but then it goes places
Kevin: you start you're you first of all
Kevin: you're like it's I think it's the first farming game where you're
Kevin: like proper driving a car
Kevin: that's interesting
Kevin: but then
Kevin: it goes all over you have relationships with
Kevin: people in the city because you do and it
Kevin: looks like a very realistic suburb
Kevin: but then but then there's
Kevin: magic at the end and hot air balloons
Kevin: and okay it's not as realistic
Kevin: as I thought but
Kevin: yeah they're doing a lot good for you
Kevin: ranchers also
Kevin: I gotta say I should have put this
Kevin: anytime there's romance in the games
Kevin: it feels like they tend to skew
Kevin: young 20s 30s
Kevin: attractive sort of people
Kevin: these models
Kevin: did not seem that attractive
Kevin: I'm sorry but that makes it stand out
Chelsea: iconic there you go sorry they're not furries kevin
Kevin: in my opinion
Kevin: um so they
Kevin: oh
Kevin: um
Kevin: and lastly
Kevin: we have village in the shade
Kevin: um
Kevin: yeah
Kevin: oh this one's sick
Kevin: because I see it
Kevin: I like the art style
Kevin: um
Kevin: it's it's
Kevin: and we're in Japan again
Kevin: hey shocker
Kevin: Kevin likes the weeb game
Kevin: um
Kevin: uh
Kevin: but then we
Kevin: that's the one
Kevin: we're returning to straight out
Kevin: horror
Kevin: um
Chelsea: oh no uh so it looks all sweet and innocent and then it ends up scary I'm out nope I can't do it
Kevin: yeah
Kevin: it's
Kevin: I'm interested
Kevin: because it looks like
Kevin: such a uh
Kevin: like just a very cutesy
Kevin: sort of game
Kevin: but the way they pivot
Kevin: it's wild
Kevin: um
Kevin: I'm
Kevin: I'm generally not a horror guy
Kevin: but I'm very interested
Kevin: how they're playing with both here
Kevin: um
Kevin: yeah I know it looks
Kevin: look there is
Kevin: blood in this trailer
Kevin: like that's
Kevin: that's the level we're talking
Kevin: like yeah
Kevin: um
Kevin: and it's out
Kevin: so I will check it out
Kevin: at some point
Kevin: village in the shade
Kevin: full of beans
Kevin: Okay, that's what came out in the last couple of months.
Kevin: Let's talk about what's coming out in the next month, or very soon.
Kevin: Actually, one of these will already be out by the time people listen.
Chelsea: Very soon. Yep. Yeah.
Kevin: Star Sand Island, August 18th, now including online multiplayer.
Kevin: That's exciting.
Kevin: That's the one Al has many thoughts and feelings on.
Kevin: And you can skateboard and do...
Kevin: Well, sadly, no, you can't do sick kickflips, but you can skateboard.
Chelsea: Oh. Oh.
Kevin: It sounds...
Kevin: It sounds alright, honestly, from everything I see and hear.
Kevin: So, go check that out.
Kevin: That's August 18th.
Kevin: It will be out by the time you people are listening to this.
Chelsea: exciting. The big one, the big one.
Kevin: Next up, the big one.
Kevin: Everyone clear out.
Kevin: Well, the semi-big one because it's the name, but it's not Story of Seasons.
Chelsea: No, yeah
Kevin: It's Harvest Moon!
Kevin: Skytree Village and the Lost Valley, now both on iOS and Android.
Kevin: Originally, both 3D
Kevin: I don't know if these games are good
Chelsea: dropped out of nowhere just like by the way y'all we're getting this is coming to uh mobile
Chelsea: I asked my husband who is a huge harvest moon fan and he's like
Kevin: Yeah, well, that's a thing, right?
Kevin: If it's Harvest Moon TM
Kevin: Then that's kind of going to be the response
Kevin: Let's see here, let's see what else
Kevin: We also have
Kevin: Well, actually, kind of
Kevin: This doesn't release next month
Kevin: Echoes of
Chelsea: - No, those are out, but the next one is delayed.
Kevin: Yeah, yeah, anti-release
Kevin: Echoes of Teradia got delayed
Kevin: Till October 18th
Kevin: Al is upset by this
Kevin: We get pictures of marriage candidates
Kevin: Wait, what do those marriage candidates look like?
Kevin: I need to see
Kevin: Let's see
Chelsea: they look like pokemon almost pokemon not pokemon like pokemon characters let me clarify
Kevin: Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh
Kevin: you know sorry that that wait there are some things that look like pokemon and not the dating
Chelsea: no no no no no you're not catching me
Kevin: candidates i'm saying there's some critters in there um again that is delayed till october which
Kevin: is uh too bad um what I was just reading some of the stuff on this website that's talking I mentioned
Kevin: i'm sad um okay um oh there's the candidates um I see them the outpost of them silly me
Kevin: Those are...
Kevin: I see what you mean by Pokemon characters.
Kevin: Yeah, that blue hair guy.
Chelsea: I don't know if it's like the shading or what, but yeah.
Kevin: Yeah, Lorelei with the purple hair.
Kevin: Yeah, it's something about the colors that just stick out.
Kevin: Yeah, yeah.
Kevin: Hank's got nice facial hair.
Kevin: I'll give him that.
Kevin: All right, let's see.
Kevin: Other games, releases coming up.
Kevin: Bunchy Days, coming out October 29th.
Kevin: It's...
Kevin: Let's see.
Kevin: Oh, this is really a cute art style we're looking at.
Kevin: Oh, we've got a Kappa.
Kevin: I'm sorry.
Kevin: I'm trying to remember what this one is here.
Chelsea: Yeah, Kappa, a little Kappa companion.
Kevin: Yeah, it's got...
Kevin: It's got a very kind of classic GBA sort of aesthetic.
Chelsea: I was going to say, it looks exactly like a Game Boy Advance game, but in a positive way, not...
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Yeah, in a positive way, yeah.
Kevin: Yeah, this is very cute.
Kevin: The animations, yeah.
Kevin: They're knocking out of the park.
Kevin: That's what they're going for.
Chelsea: Yeah.
Kevin: Yeah, help take care of that Kappa.
Kevin: Yeah, Dunchy Days.
Kevin: Yeah, that's actually intriguing.
Kevin: Okay, and that is, again, October 29th.
Kevin: All right, next up, we have Farming Camp, September 24th.
Kevin: That is around the corner, because time goes way too fast.
Kevin: We've got...
Kevin: This is the one where...
Kevin: This isn't like a magical camp.
Kevin: Yeah, it is.
Kevin: Okay.
Chelsea: yeah so here's a description on steam it says plant crops care for adorable animals complete
Chelsea: fun mini games and help restore the camp while building lasting friendships along the way
Chelsea: whether you're working together with fellow campers or competing and friendly challenges
Chelsea: every day brings new adventures and memories to make which really narrows it down in the cozy
Chelsea: game community but no it looks cute yeah september 24th
Kevin: Yeah, it looks better than I remember because I remember we talked about this one before.
Kevin: Does it got on the top?
Kevin: I don't know.
Chelsea: The guy in a top hat.
Kevin: Yeah, the chickens are very round and cute.
Kevin: I'm down for this.
Kevin: I'm interested.
Kevin: I'll keep an eye on it.
Kevin: The camp is an interesting setting trying to play that angle.
Chelsea: - Yeah.
Kevin: Oh, God.
Kevin: Next up, we have a winner winner because it's Frog Island.
Chelsea: - Frog Island!
Kevin: Yeah, it's how should I put this?
Kevin: It's it's like that bunny game.
Kevin: I forget the one.
Kevin: It's the one Kelly.
Kevin: I think Kelly or Maddie played it.
Chelsea: Oh, uh, I played it too. Usagi Shima? Yeah, The Bunny Village.
Kevin: Yeah, that's the one.
Kevin: Yeah, it looks like that, but frogs, to be very frank.
Chelsea: Oh my god. Yes.
Kevin: But I mean, go off, Chelsea.
Kevin: I thought it was a frog queen, so.
Chelsea: I'm actually not. Every Wednesday, I post, it is Wednesday, my dudes. And only a few people know
Kevin: I mean, it's frog.
Chelsea: what that is. It's a huge vine thing. And it turned into this internet meme with frogs and
Chelsea: unfortunately, this game does not release on a Wednesday. It releases on a Thursday. I just
Chelsea: checked on my daughter's birthday. But yeah, cottagecore frogs and every, yeah, frogs are
Kevin: Oh, oh.
Chelsea: just great. And if this is anything like Usagi Shima, then that's perfect.
Kevin: Yeah, which I don't know.
Kevin: It feels like it.
Kevin: There's some stuff going on.
Kevin: There's a rhythm part in there.
Kevin: I don't know what's going on there, but it's Frog Island.
Chelsea: Oh my goodness, the bus.
Kevin: Like that title, I think, says it very clearly.
Chelsea: Frog?
Kevin: All right.
Kevin: And that is against August 20th.
Kevin: That's soon.
Chelsea: Yep.
Kevin: Wait, is that out?
Kevin: No, Thursday.
Kevin: It's like the day after this comes out.
Kevin: Yeah, yeah.
Chelsea: Yep, one day after.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: Gosh, it's already the 20th.
Kevin: Oh, my gosh.
Kevin: August is going by too fast now.
Kevin: Next up, September 7th.
Kevin: Tiny Eden has announced their release date.
Kevin: That's the one where you're in an apartment.
Kevin: A small, one-bedroom apartment.
Kevin: And you're growing, farming, and gardening.
Kevin: Not farming, gardening, I guess.
Kevin: Windowsill gardening.
Kevin: Yeah, that's...
Kevin: You know, I will, again, applaud them for doing a different sort of setting.
Kevin: It's not the big, expansive farm.
Chelsea: No, it's cute, and there's a cat in the trailer thumbnail, so...
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Yeah, it is a good cat.
Kevin: I don't see the cat in the game, though.
Kevin: That's an issue if it's not.
Kevin: All right, that's September 7th.
Kevin: Okay, Ova Magica console releases coming out September 8th.
Kevin: That's where we got slimes of all kinds, little round dudes.
Kevin: I mean, this one's already been out on stage.
Chelsea: Oh, everyone's round. Why is everyone so round?
Kevin: Yeah, because that's Ova Magica.
Kevin: It's slime rain
Kevin: Sure, but not
Kevin: More emphasis on the ranching
Kevin: Yeah, it is very cute
Kevin: I haven't played it, but it's one of the ones I've wanted to
Kevin: Very exciting
Kevin: It's going to be on consoles
Kevin: What consoles is that?
Kevin: I'm assuming just all of them
Kevin: Yeah, it's all of them
Chelsea: Switch, PlayStation, Xbox, yeah.
Kevin: Alright
Chelsea: Oh, sorry.
Kevin: There you go
Chelsea: Nintendo Switch, Nintendo Switch 2, PlayStation, and Xbox.
Chelsea: Yes.
Kevin: Oh, and retail
Chelsea: And physical editions will be shipped to all backers.
Chelsea: Cool.
Kevin: Good for them
Chelsea: Yeah.
Kevin: Alright, next up
Kevin: Another console release
Kevin: Kynseed
Kevin: Let's see, which one is this one?
Kevin: I don't have to
Kevin: Oh man, I love this
Kevin: Art style, I forgot about this one
Kevin: Yeah, I remember now
Kevin: It's 2D pixel art, but it's very
Kevin: Detailed, very lush art style
Kevin: There's some wild
Kevin: Almost cartoony character designs
Kevin: in there, which I kind of love.
Kevin: Oh, it's got like a interesting battle system.
Kevin: Got like three guys.
Kevin: It's like four on four.
Kevin: Yeah, I can see.
Kevin: Yeah, that one's it's caught my eye.
Kevin: The fact that it's coming out on consoles will help now.
Kevin: Oh, wait, that's already up now.
Chelsea: out now 20 off steam though as of today so it's 3255
Kevin: I missed it.
Kevin: Well, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Kevin: That's exciting.
Kevin: Oh, oh, that.
Kevin: Hmm.
Kevin: Cool.
Kevin: That's.
Kevin: Yeah, it's hard to argue that it doesn't count, but if not, you can wait for.
Kevin: Oh, switch or consoles, all that stuff.
Kevin: I mean, it's out.
Kevin: Anyways, sorry.
Kevin: I mean, I lost because I got confused for a second is next up Village in the Shade, which
Kevin: we talked about, but it's coming out in English.
Chelsea: Yes, you cannot change your display language.
Kevin: There's an official.
Kevin: Yeah, that that sounds important.
Kevin: Al's note is correct.
Kevin: Changing language is complicated.
Kevin: Especially when you're going to English.
Kevin: Um, but the official patch for English, French and Spanish will launch on Tuesday, October
Kevin: 27.
Kevin: Um, so it's going to be a minute, but, uh, I'll wait for that, I guess.
Kevin: I didn't realize it was not out in English.
Kevin: Um, but that's fine.
Kevin: Um, that's close enough to Halloween.
Kevin: They should have just done, waited a few days just for the bit, but say love me.
Chelsea: Oh, yeah.
Kevin: Oh, okay.
Chelsea: Maybe I'll take a plunge.
Chelsea: I'm not a huge horror person in general.
Kevin: I mean, I'm not either, but, uh, I like horror when they mix it with something else, um, especially
Chelsea: But, like...
Kevin: comedy.
Kevin: Um, uh, and so that's why I'm looking at this.
Kevin: I'm intrigued because there is still clearly a cutesy, like farming game in there and looks
Kevin: solid.
Kevin: The art style looks great.
Kevin: Um, um, but then, yeah, they, they lean hard into the horn.
Kevin: I'm curious how those two will play.
Kevin: So, yeah, October, I'll be waiting for that.
Kevin: Will it be that?
Kevin: That is not enough time to do an episode for Halloween, though, sadly.
Chelsea: No!
Kevin: I digress.
Kevin: But either way, it will be covered probably one day, maybe.
Kevin: But, OK, that's all the game dates and release dates and all that stuff coming out.
Kevin: There's a lot of them, a lot of good ones, actually.
Kevin: Pretty good, healthy roster, I will say.
Kevin: Let's talk about stuff that is out.
Kevin: game updates starting with
Kevin: Pocopia. Did you hear that the DLC
Kevin: that the
Kevin: game update, the free game
Kevin: update is out and that the paid DLC
Kevin: expansion is out. It's all out now.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Again, I'll be doing a full and
Kevin: death episode.
Kevin: I do think some
Kevin: of these free stuff is nice.
Kevin: Obviously, the underwater
Kevin: mechanics do apply
Kevin: to free players, not just
Kevin: the DLC. But also, they've done
Kevin: like I mentioned, the trash can.
Kevin: There's a fun one they snuck in there called
Kevin: the Portal Pod.
Kevin: As I've
Kevin: discussed before, it has a
Kevin: Pocopia. It basically has the Minecraft system where
Kevin: every storage
Kevin: chest or whatever is
Kevin: just independent.
Kevin: If you want to find something stored
Kevin: in a certain box, you have to travel to that location.
Kevin: Which,
Kevin: with living screens,
Kevin: I can see a little people a little bothered by it.
Kevin: I get it. Portal Pod
Kevin: is the way to go around
Kevin: that. You can now set up a
Kevin: connected storage box between
Kevin: areas called the Portal Pod,
Kevin: which is very helpful.
Chelsea: Okay, well, Tandy, at least.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: I haven't used it because I'm not weak.
Kevin: I'm kidding.
Chelsea: Oh!
Kevin: No, it's fine.
Chelsea: The fake fan.
Kevin: I get where people want it.
Kevin: It's good.
Kevin: Just throw it up in your house.
Kevin: Like my brother Calvin already
Kevin: using it.
Kevin: He's basically all his
Kevin: materials that he would
Kevin: carry on for his person.
Kevin: Now he just stores it in there,
Kevin: which makes sense.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: But yeah, Pocopia.
Kevin: It's out.
Kevin: And there's
Kevin: the floating blocks
Kevin: is another cool one.
Kevin: I think
Kevin: it's part of the
Kevin: paid DLC,
Kevin: but you can build
Kevin: structures kind of
Kevin: floating in
Kevin: in the water
Kevin: environments.
Kevin: I'm interested to see
Kevin: if they'll
Kevin: expand that to
Kevin: the
Kevin: non-water
Kevin: environments,
Kevin: just have floating
Kevin: structures.
Kevin: You can kind of
Chelsea: Oh, that would be neat.
Kevin: do that now,
Kevin: it requires some
Kevin: effort,
Kevin: but it would be
Kevin: cool just to see
Kevin: floating blocks,
Kevin: floating structures.
Chelsea: - I know, I'm getting major FOMO, not having it.
Kevin: Look,
Kevin: look,
Kevin: once Switch 2
Kevin: with the Zelda
Kevin: drops,
Kevin: that's your time
Kevin: to get in,
Chelsea: Yeah, that's totally my strategy.
Chelsea: I was just waiting for Zelda 2, for Zelda to drop.
Kevin: Yeah, well, there you go.
Kevin: Yeah, Pocopia's good.
Kevin: And hey, there'll be another surge
Kevin: because this expansion pass is a three-parter.
Kevin: The second one doesn't sound that, yeah.
Chelsea: Oh, is that it?
Kevin: The second one doesn't sound that big as of right now.
Kevin: It's not a new location.
Kevin: But the third one will, I believe,
Kevin: confirm to be another location.
Kevin: So there'll be another point
Kevin: when there'll be a little hype wave
Kevin: and you can jump in.
Chelsea: Perfect.
Kevin: Yeah, but also it's Pocopia
Kevin: and it's just eternally, I think so.
Chelsea: Well, that's fair, yeah.
Kevin: Let's see.
Kevin: It's out already.
Kevin: Snacko, version 1.2.
Kevin: Better heart events, more dialogue flair,
Kevin: better stability.
Kevin: These are all very good things.
Kevin: Not requiring guessing for heart events.
Kevin: That's on where and when.
Kevin: Wait, what?
Kevin: That was, that's while that was existed.
Kevin: Yeah, it should be very clear
Kevin: like when you're going to do that.
Kevin: That seems very important.
Kevin: But the dialogue flair, that's, man,
Kevin: ever see that where they
Kevin: like improving the dialogue
Kevin: that's great yeah that's
Kevin: fantastic yeah and
Kevin: stability I mean yeah
Kevin: needless to say stability
Kevin: is always better but well
Kevin: yeah I mean snack oh it's
Kevin: the game where you're the
Kevin: cat and very cute and
Kevin: whatnot there's on the
Kevin: Steam page they go in
Kevin: depth of all the details of
Kevin: these updates but that's a
Kevin: pretty solid patch overall
Kevin: yeah good stuff mm-hmm
Chelsea: No, I like their transparency, too, with all that.
Chelsea: No, that's good.
Kevin: good good job snack oh
Kevin: next up to celebrate Codey
Kevin: graduating research to
Kevin: decide to release a patch
Kevin: version also 1.2 strangely
Kevin: enough we have a research
Kevin: story adding two new
Kevin: look I can love
Kevin: capybaras don't get me
Kevin: wrong I'm just it's so
Kevin: ubiquitous it feels like I
Kevin: don't know what it is in
Kevin: flashcore games but uh
Kevin: capy bearers added to
Kevin: research story now I will
Kevin: say they're usually not
Kevin: rideable but they're
Kevin: rideable here I don't
Kevin: think that logistically
Kevin: works in the real life
Kevin: capybaras are not that
Kevin: big but uh you you do you
Kevin: I guess research story
Chelsea: use your imagination first of all they call it the clay pea bara
Kevin: or is it the clappy or oh
Kevin: it is clappy bara yeah
Kevin: there's a wine there yeah
Chelsea: yeah it looks like clay adorable
Kevin: you're right um it is and
Kevin: then there's the mossy
Kevin: what I don't know what I'm
Kevin: about that I'm all right um it
Kevin: it relaxes in the hot spring
Kevin: yeah that's cool I like I
Chelsea: Oh my gosh.
Chelsea: I love it.
Kevin: yeah capybaras are cute I've
Kevin: never seen one in real life but
Chelsea: No?
Kevin: yeah I can't think unless at a
Kevin: zoo maybe I can't think off the
Chelsea: They're just chilling.
Kevin: top of my head yeah that's
Chelsea: They chill.
Kevin: probably why they're in these
Kevin: all these cottagecore games
Kevin: aside from the the the happy we
Kevin: got uh all sorts of new six new
Kevin: farm buildings for automation
Kevin: as we do
Kevin: in farming games
Kevin: let's see there's this clay silo
Kevin: that refills auto feeders
Kevin: it automatically refills
Kevin: auto feeders that's okay
Kevin: that's automating your
Kevin: automation that's cool
Kevin: question I was always happy
Chelsea: How far can we go?
Kevin: to explore
Kevin: let's see creature enhancement areas
Kevin: oh this is cool
Kevin: that kind of auto-maintains creativity.
Kevin: Jupiter happiness, different little environments for them.
Kevin: I like that, actually.
Kevin: And then a magical spa late-game building
Kevin: that gives a passive daily happiness bonus.
Kevin: That sounds all right.
Kevin: I could use a spa.
Kevin: They also have advanced soils and silt.
Kevin: I think that's actually cool.
Kevin: Anything that makes farming a little more day
Kevin: and I make more knobs, you can turn.
Kevin: I like that a lot, actually.
Kevin: And then they've introduced
Kevin: Relaxed Game Mode
Kevin: Permanent Fast Travel
Kevin: Wait, there was not permanent before?
Kevin: Oh, that's cool
Kevin: But anyway, so yeah
Kevin: Lower the stress
Kevin: Make things more convenient
Kevin: Quality of life
Kevin: All that good stuff
Kevin: Looks like they're doing a lot of it
Kevin: And it's also launching on Nintendo Switch
Kevin: On August 27th
Chelsea: Oh, it's coming up.
Kevin: That's exciting
Kevin: Yep, that's all on Steam page
Kevin: That's pretty hefty
Kevin: That's a good one, research story
Kevin: Good on you
Kevin: So that's good stuff
Kevin: Wait, is that going to
Kevin: Nintendo Switch is going to release
Kevin: I'm going to assume it's releasing
Kevin: With all that stuff
Kevin: I believe it is
Kevin: Okay, moving on
Kevin: Disney Dreamlight Valley
Kevin: Who is it this time?
Kevin: Okay, this one I'm actually not shocked
Kevin: That he wasn't in already
Kevin: But good old Wreck-It Ralph
Chelsea: Wreck it, Ralph.
Kevin: The big man himself
Kevin: Is in there
Kevin: And of course, you know this means
Kevin: No, they will not be addressing
Kevin: Any of the video game licenses
Kevin: That way they touch
Chelsea: no
Kevin: no you
Chelsea: no you do not
Kevin: sonic the hedgehog or zanky you know you do get uh you get to build an arcade you get a little
Kevin: arcade furniture the the house is uh sugar rush is probably in there you get the sugar rush clothing
Kevin: um man I love rick and ralph so much one oh great
Chelsea: Yeah, it is really good.
Chelsea: When my daughter broke her leg, that's like all she, that's all she wanted to watch.
Kevin: Oh, that's, oh, well, I'm glad it helped us.
Chelsea: Got us through the tough days.
Kevin: That was a good one.
Kevin: Let's see.
Kevin: What is, they also mentioned best friends.
Kevin: What is best friends?
Kevin: Strengthen your bonds of your favorite villagers to unlock special perks, bonuses, and exciting
Kevin: ways to spend time together throughout the valley.
Kevin: Well, there's a whole blog thing.
Kevin: I won't get too in depth with that, but that's, that's interesting.
Kevin: Wreck-a-Roth, good to pick.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Oh, God.
Kevin: Let's see here.
Kevin: Next up.
Kevin: Wait, what on earth?
Kevin: I didn't, I didn't catch.
Kevin: Oh, my gosh.
Kevin: Luma Island.
Kevin: I love unexpected crossovers.
Chelsea: Heck yeah.
Chelsea: What on earth?
Chelsea: Look at that.
Kevin: We're getting a big free summertime update on Luma Island.
Kevin: And, you know, there's a whole bunch of cosmetics and, and all sorts of stuff.
Kevin: Beach parties.
Kevin: Um, but, uh, who, who do we call when we really want that summer vibe going?
Kevin: None other than Dave the Diver.
Chelsea: the dave the dave name a more iconic collab
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: He's, he's, he's been to Nikkei.
Kevin: He's, he's hung out with Godzilla and, and, and Yakuza, and now heading down to Luma Island.
Kevin: Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Kevin: Um, help him get home, help him fish stuff.
Kevin: It's Dave the Diver.
Kevin: Just, just hanging out.
Kevin: Um, he's on, he needs a vacation.
Chelsea: He's on vacation.
Kevin: Poor Dave.
Kevin: He works too hard.
Chelsea: Give him a break.
Kevin: Ha, ha, ha.
Kevin: Did you play Dave the Diver?
Chelsea: Uh, it's on my playlist.
Kevin: Okay.
Kevin: That's a good one.
Kevin: Um, good stuff.
Chelsea: Yeah.
Kevin: Luma, that, oh, okay.
Chelsea: That took you off guard.
Kevin: Yeah, it did.
Kevin: Um, man, there's a whole thing.
Kevin: There's a lot of weird, unexpected.
Kevin: Unexpected crossover is going on right now, but, oh, that's a separate topic.
Kevin: Anyways, back on topic.
Kevin: Next up, we have Traveler's Rest, our, our, uh, good old tavern, uh, quote unquote simulator,
Kevin: but you're doing everything else.
Kevin: Um, we have rum and runes update.
Kevin: Why did you, you're literally a tavern.
Kevin: Why did you not have rum before?
Kevin: I do enjoy rum.
Kevin: Probably one of my favorite alcohols.
Kevin: I like a coconut run that's it's kind of my go to I don't know what else to get but anyways
Kevin: um uh so yeah there's there's but the rune part is probably more interesting because they got
Kevin: arcane arts um and there is uh the hollow a new city area dark suburb where shady deals and it's
Kevin: the dark web but real basically um yeah that that's cool that's actually kind of cool little
Kevin: dark shady area new spells grimoires etc etc all right
Kevin: arcane stuff yeah no it's it's gotten places it's taken a while um but traveler's rest looks
Chelsea: - Oh, how would I play this?
Kevin: all right actually um it's still early access but uh you know they're hey they're still working on
Kevin: it I'll give them that it's been a while but they're working on it um uh yeah one at a time
Chelsea: One day at a time.
Kevin: so wait did we get a date for that
Chelsea: Oh.
Chelsea: I don't see an update.
Kevin: I i didn't either yeah I didn't either um wait did luma island have an update when did dave come
Chelsea: Like, I don't see a date.
Kevin: yeah oh no it's it's available luma island is available and I forgot to say that but uh
Chelsea: You're doing that right when we're done this.
Kevin: you probably um oh that's that's tempting but maybe
Chelsea: Or I don't know if I couldn't do your Yu-Gi-Oh time.
Kevin: well yeah actually no the other stuff is stuff that's out I think
Kevin: isn't that yeah game updates yeah um anyway sorry let's see here next up we have uh apico
Kevin: Bugle Month continues
Kevin: actually surprised because
Kevin: they're fixing
Chelsea: Round two!
Kevin: bugs although
Kevin: one would argue they're
Kevin: already peak how could you improve
Kevin: them
Kevin: yeah
Kevin: but yeah now there's a whole bunch of technical
Kevin: and in diff
Kevin: bugs and quality of life stuff
Kevin: go check it out
Kevin: it's live
Kevin: let's see here
Kevin: next up we have
Kevin: Bitter Harvest is already at 1.5
Kevin: That's the game. I'm just
Kevin: shocked. It's that
Kevin: far in because that did not feel like that long ago
Chelsea: That's pretty quick already.
Kevin: it came out. Yeah.
Kevin: Wait, what do you mean full
Kevin: home decoration? I feel like that should have
Kevin: already been in there, but that's fine. Chairs
Kevin: and couches,
Kevin: beds, tables. That's a lot of
Kevin: items that they're adding. That's good.
Chelsea: I feel like that might be a day one thing you'd think
Kevin: Deeper.
Chelsea: though, right? Like, I don't know.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Yeah, you, well,
Kevin: that's pottage, Cor.
Chelsea: Those premium, yeah, no,
Kevin: You'd think.
Chelsea: the furniture expansion pack.
Kevin: Where?
Kevin: Or another way. Where is the
Kevin: real 1.0?
Kevin: Either way, you want to look
Kevin: at that. Yes.
Kevin: That says cottage, Cor.
Kevin: Yeah, and deeper minds.
Kevin: That's fine, I guess. I haven't played
Kevin: Bitter Harvest, I don't know.
Kevin: Out now.
Kevin: Probably winning
Kevin: the award for the best
Kevin: update name because it's
Kevin: sheer brilliance, but sheer
Kevin: as in cheering sheep.
Chelsea: yeah I have this game I started it and man it's so cute and wholesome like there's no
Chelsea: there's no direction you need to go you're just going based on vibes
Chelsea: it's great you drive an enormous b bug month continued
Kevin: It is very cute
Chelsea: um oh my god it's really really cute and I like I love the update name
Kevin: I'm kind of shocked that horses and sheep
Kevin: weren't already in it
Kevin: I love sheep
Kevin: How do they have axolotls before sheep?
Kevin: That's wild
Kevin: And platypus
Chelsea: and platypus
Kevin: I love platypi
Chelsea: why i'm playing this lame i'm playing as i'm just my character is a teddy bear
Kevin: Oh, that's...
Chelsea: like I tried at the cost customization and I just could not pick so I said you know what
Chelsea: for this one i'll just do teddy bear it is so cute
Kevin: That's a safe bet.
Kevin: I do love bears.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: They're adding physics, some character dynamics,
Kevin: flopping ears and wiggling tails and all that,
Kevin: and a whole bunch of other bug fixes and improvements, et cetera, et cetera.
Kevin: Yeah, Posey Caravan.
Kevin: Good for you.
Kevin: That's a fun little update there.
Kevin: New animals are hype.
Kevin: Next up, we have Little Witch in the Woods.
Kevin: Is the first page a new update?
Kevin: This is kind of a wild one.
Kevin: They're revamping the prologue and the opening of the game.
Kevin: I mean, that's cool if it needed to be reworked.
Kevin: It's like, how do you deliver that to existing players?
Kevin: And they talk about it in the Steam post.
Chelsea: Well, this is here. Starting a new game will allow you to experience a new opening and prologue. Loading an existing prologue save will play a partially updated version of the original prologue. A guide pop up will appear when loading an existing prologue save. Interesting. So you can still kind of see it if you don't want to start your whole game over again.
Kevin: yeah that which is interesting um that's a weird challenge to have to deal with but uh but uh I mean
Kevin: hey they improved it good for them I guess yeah it's a little witch in the woods um that is out
Kevin: now already um
Kevin: yeah I think it's out
Chelsea: Oh, there's a lot on this update.
Chelsea: Yeah, I think it's already...
Chelsea: It's ready, yeah.
Kevin: oh oh yeah I mean it sounds like a good time to get in with it better
Chelsea: This kind of piqued my interest.
Kevin: opening so why not um I love their little art on the the like the update the image um it's very cute
Kevin: I i don't know if the game is that cute though but um anyways whoa first we saw the next
Kevin: hello okay
Chelsea: Hello, look at that.
Kevin: tales of secu um shrine of love update uh it's it's live um it just came out but it's already live
Kevin: Okay, so there's a stratagem.
Kevin: The Inari Shrine, where you can...
Kevin: Here, I'm just going to read it.
Kevin: I like how they did this language.
Kevin: Visit the Inari Shrine to weave the threads of fate
Kevin: and adjust your relationships with Sekiyu's romance-able villagers.
Kevin: You will now be able to use the Inari Shrine
Kevin: to break up with a partner you're romantically committed to,
Kevin: get divorced, and even pursue romance with villagers
Kevin: you've previously rejected.
Kevin: Just make sure you've got the right offerings at hand.
Chelsea: is divorce a common like is that kind of a that's not really a mechanic in other games is it
Kevin: Kind of like...
Kevin: It's getting there, I would say.
Kevin: I think it's...
Kevin: If it's not there at launch, it's usually added in later.
Kevin: Yeah, I mean, Stardew did it, and everyone kind of followed suit,
Kevin: I would say.
Kevin: But managing it all at Shrine is kind of interesting
Kevin: and kind of a fun way to handle it.
Kevin: And, you know, use resources to manage your relationships.
Kevin: If only...
Kevin: We're that easy.
Kevin: IRL, but alas.
Kevin: That's why this game's magical.
Kevin: But now you can spend the night with your spouse,
Kevin: which, you know, I'll say,
Kevin: I don't think I've seen another game do.
Kevin: You can spend the night with your spouse
Kevin: when you interact in the marital bed.
Kevin: You cuddle up and, you know,
Kevin: there's nothing, it's nothing risque or whatever,
Kevin: but you're lying down in bed with your partner
Kevin: are injured.
Kevin: I guess kind of somewhat underwear-ish look.
Kevin: That's probably the boldest.
Chelsea: well obviously they're just playing tic-tac-toe like what else do you do in bed with your spouse
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Exactly.
Kevin: I don't think I've seen any other game we've covered on this podcast, Tackle That.
Kevin: So that's, you know what?
Kevin: All right.
Kevin: Why not?
Kevin: That's one way to differentiate yourself.
Kevin: I am not fair to say
Kevin: you continues to impress and
Kevin: terrify me a little bit
Kevin: um but
Chelsea: Okay, I love the next bullet point.
Kevin: okay and see this is where we go
Chelsea: Yo-kai scarecrow improvements.
Kevin: right back to improving to amazing
Kevin: me because you got a little yokai
Kevin: scarecrow hopping around um
Kevin: and they help fertilize
Kevin: and grow crops and
Kevin: that looks pretty cool I'm not gonna
Kevin: like um little
Kevin: dude just hopping around I like it
Kevin: crafting from chest they didn't have that before
Kevin: oh my goodness um
Kevin: sorry I'm just looking there's a lot of
Chelsea: So you had to have it right in your inventory before?
Kevin: things in this update
Kevin: I'm guessing so yes
Kevin: um and there's quick transfer
Kevin: from store oh they didn't have quick transfer oh come
Kevin: on guys come on
Kevin: um I digress
Kevin: uh rename your heart farm
Kevin: uh change your body type
Kevin: that's
Kevin: cool
Kevin: oh it looks like they
Kevin: now basically you can customize everything
Kevin: you couldn't before, including your
Kevin: body type, but you can do that whenever
Kevin: now, so that's nice. Very interesting
Kevin: updates, very cool. Holy
Kevin: moly, next one, shocking
Kevin: me even more.
Chelsea: we made this episode just for you
Kevin: It's the year's 2026,
Chelsea: just for Kevin
Kevin: and
Kevin: Paleo Pines is getting an
Chelsea: heck yeah
Kevin: update.
Chelsea: player's choice kickstarter
Kevin: What?
Kevin: The Kickstarter people got to help design colors?
Kevin: That's so cool.
Kevin: Oh, they finally have decks for
Kevin: all those colors and
Kevin: skins.
Kevin: The Dino
Kevin: decks, basically, now with the colors, and you can
Kevin: track them. That's really
Kevin: helpful, because that was probably one of the big
Kevin: differentiators. It wasn't a huge Dino
Kevin: decks to begin with, but you could get
Kevin: so many different colors and variations.
Kevin: Oh, what? They have saddle
Kevin: bags that can carry items?
Kevin: Oh, my goodness.
Chelsea: No, most important, small dinos can now be assigned to composters to pick up poop for you.
Kevin: That's pretty good.
Chelsea: Don't put that in the fine print.
Chelsea: That needs to be front and center.
Kevin: yeah that was kind of a big
Kevin: tour too actually that's kind of a
Chelsea: That's really good.
Kevin: big deal
Kevin: yeah because you had to maintain
Kevin: the pens and that took
Kevin: work so you know
Kevin: that took time that's pretty good
Kevin: man these small
Kevin: dinos doing a lot they can find wild
Kevin: collectibles and carry them for you oh my goodness
Kevin: new crops
Kevin: this is massive
Kevin: holy moly recipes
Kevin: some decor
Kevin: items, yada, yada, yada.
Kevin: A compass item.
Kevin: What? To help you find some?
Kevin: That's fantastic. Sometimes the map
Kevin: was a little confusing.
Kevin: Auto sort the inventory with a button.
Kevin: Skip to the next time of day.
Kevin: Oh my goodness, this is a lot.
Kevin: Wow, it's going down the list here.
Kevin: That's pretty cool.
Kevin: Yeah, I love Paleo Pines, of course.
Kevin: That's a big update.
Kevin: That's almost enough to get...
Kevin: That might get me back in. I never actually finished that game.
Kevin: Yeah, no, that's a recommend.
Kevin: It had its issues, but a lot of those issues
Kevin: are being addressed here.
Chelsea: Seems like it.
Chelsea: Yeah, it seems like a good time to get started.
Kevin: Yeah, Paleo Pines.
Kevin: Good for you. I didn't know they were still going.
Chelsea: Maybe I'll do that.
Kevin: Dang.
Chelsea: Oh, is it only PC?
Kevin: I don't know.
Chelsea: I don't know.
Chelsea: Let's see.
Kevin: I don't think so.
Kevin: Let me see.
Chelsea: Oh, no.
Chelsea: Nintendo Switch, PS4, PS5, Xbox One.
Kevin: Yeah, okay.
Kevin: Yeah, it's on there.
Chelsea: X and X.
Chelsea: Oh, it's older.
Chelsea: It's 2023.
Kevin: Yeah, no, that's why I'm shocked.
Chelsea: Oh, I'm behind.
Kevin: Yeah.
Chelsea: I'm behind on the times here.
Kevin: Yeah, no.
Chelsea: I thought it was a newer game.
Kevin: Oh, no, no.
Kevin: This is a while ago.
Kevin: It was, I believe, it was our game of the year that year, actually.
Kevin: Was it?
Kevin: No, I can't remember.
Kevin: No, was that the year Sock?
Kevin: I'm not singing that.
Kevin: Manico won.
Kevin: I don't remember, regardless.
Kevin: I think it was the year Manico won.
Chelsea: Okay.
Kevin: Anyways, yeah, that was a while ago.
Kevin: That's what I'm shocked.
Kevin: Like, we'll update this late in the game.
Chelsea: Wow.
Kevin: Good for them.
Chelsea: That's like when Animal Crossing just dropped a whole new thing with the hotel.
Kevin: Yeah, the Welcome Amiibo, oh my gosh, that was possibly one of the best updates.
Kevin: It's ever done in a video game.
Kevin: That was incredible.
Chelsea: yeah by the way you can have a hotel now turn your game on it's there
Kevin: They just shadow dropped it, too, basically.
Kevin: Oh, yeah.
Kevin: Yeah.
Kevin: Good for you, Paleo Pines.
Kevin: Yeah, that's certainly getting me to turn it on.
Kevin: Okay, next up, last one, Stardew Valley, Nintendo Switch 2 Physical Edition, going to be through
Kevin: Fangamer, coming February 5th in 2027.
Kevin: It's going to take some time, I guess, but they got the Year Standard, they got the Deluxe
Kevin: Edition, actually the Deluxe Edition, oh, no, the Deluxe might be sold out or not available,
Kevin: I don't know.
Kevin: Yeah, Switch, Switch 2, it looks like it comes with a little instruction manual, that's pretty
Chelsea: I miss when games always had the little manual with them.
Kevin: awesome.
Kevin: Yeah, I do, too.
Kevin: I got to say, Guardians Rune Factory, the Guardians of Awesome, I didn't talk about that on the
Kevin: episode but that game
Kevin: actually came with an
Kevin: manual my physical
Kevin: edition which blew my
Kevin: mind and it was like
Chelsea: Did it intimidate you a little bit like, oh, crap.
Kevin: no no it was like good
Kevin: it was like it was
Kevin: flavorful it was like
Kevin: somebody's journal and
Kevin: had like told you
Kevin: everything out like all
Kevin: the mechanics and
Kevin: characters and even had
Kevin: the little space for
Kevin: notes in the back
Kevin: yes exactly yeah no
Chelsea: oh I love when games did that like find your own discovery and put it in your little guide at the back
Kevin: azuma did killed it with
Kevin: anyway so stardew valley
Kevin: will probably be getting
Kevin: that um this little
Kevin: little indie game felt
Kevin: started okay um so that
Kevin: that was technically our
Kevin: last one but I actually
Kevin: just little little asterisk
Kevin: a little side note here
Kevin: um uh we missed it
Kevin: because it came out
Kevin: during bug month but
Kevin: stardew valley actually
Kevin: had a magic the gathering
Kevin: collab um yep oh
Chelsea: no way
Kevin: uh are you familiar with
Chelsea: oh no I haven't played magic in I don't even know how long I was super into it and then they started
Chelsea: doing all these collabs with like lord of the rings and stuff but i'm like you know what
Kevin: yep yep
Chelsea: I don't know if I can I might have to get back into it okay what's the stardew one
Kevin: okay it's it's I mean it's it's no it's really bad in in magic right now the collab stuff um
Kevin: in in this year in 2026 or the last year I don't remember they released more uh
Chelsea: My jellies.
Kevin: they released more non-magic stuff than magic stuff is wild um anyways um but then you get
Kevin: sometimes you get one like this that just hits and it's hard to argue that right
Kevin: Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Kevin: Um, uh, so yeah, okay, so Marvel, or Magic the Gathering does a, um, uh, do these releases
Kevin: of products called Secret Layers.
Kevin: Um, they are, uh, basically packs of six to seven-ish cards.
Kevin: It's not a full set release.
Kevin: Um, it's just a, a, a batch of cards.
Kevin: Um, and sometimes they'll release different batches at once, um, like for Star
Kevin: Dew Valley, they released three or four different batches.
Kevin: Um, they call it a super drop because they drop them all at once and you can pick which
Kevin: ones you want or buy them all.
Kevin: Um, but, uh, basically a lot, most, the majority of the Stardew Valley and Secret Layers work
Kevin: like this, uh, Stardew Valley cards, they're, uh, they're re-skins or, or, or, or different
Kevin: artworks on existing card effects.
Kevin: Uh, Magic the Gathering is pricey in general.
Kevin: Secret Layers are no exception.
Kevin: Um, like,
Kevin: it was a hundred USD for buying everything, like, uh, and foil or whatever.
Kevin: Um, if I recall, Al did, in fact, acquire them or buy, purchase them.
Kevin: My brother, Calvin, also actually acquired them and foil.
Kevin: So, there you go, Al.
Chelsea: Oh my goodness.
Kevin: You, you, you didn't, you didn't best him.
Kevin: Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Kevin: Uh, he, he actually just got the cards this past week.
Kevin: Um, and I will say, like, they're pretty good.
Kevin: Like, the art quality.
Chelsea: Yeah, I'm looking at them now. That's a cool, like, yeah.
Kevin: Yeah, I
Kevin: The one that really
Kevin: Takes the cake is Stardew
Kevin: Valley, which is a card in itself
Kevin: It's a land
Kevin: As it should be, has a special
Kevin: Effects, that one is a brand new
Kevin: Card design
Kevin: I mean, if you want, I don't
Chelsea: cute would you like me to read what it does okay i'm looking i'm just okay add one to the
Chelsea: mana pool i'm assuming to have an untapped creature you control create a food token
Chelsea: choose target permanent you control draw a card then another player of your choice may
Chelsea: gain control of that permanent activate only as a sorcery interesting
Kevin: that see that's that's kind of fun it's like you're selling something that's what it is
Chelsea: yeah like you could take my creature oh
Kevin: like selling food or an animal that's cute yeah that's cute I like that we i'm i'm game for that
Chelsea: we need to do a magic greenhouse
Chelsea: I haven't played I haven't played since like innistrad I think was my last set which was like 2011
Kevin: as well i'm not as well versed but uh oh I think they just went back to innistrad this year
Chelsea: oh okay
Kevin: actually yeah but um it's coming I don't know it's relatively soon
Kevin: but uh yeah no that super drop came that magic set came out I uh yeah like I said the art a lot
Kevin: of the art was in fact done by concerned ape himself so it's it's pretty rad um and yeah
Kevin: calvin got it the cards look stardew valley itself looks pretty nice all night anyways but yeah I just
Kevin: one oh oh you have and felix the cat and the office
Chelsea: There's a Garfield one?!
Chelsea: Hold on. I am so... what? Okay, I'm so... I'm so out of touch here.
Kevin: yeah no that's yeah I mean the hobbits out right now last year we had
Chelsea: I'm so out. I'm kidding. I know. I'm weirded in, I'm not weirded out.
Chelsea: Interesting. Wow, they've really been going at it.
Chelsea: Garfield. Yeah, Felix the Cat. My Little Pony?!
Kevin: oh yeah the see see because the secret layers aren't full uh sets they can you know it's just
Chelsea: Okay, yeah, yeah.
Kevin: five or six cards of whatever they want and oh they do a hatsune miku one like every year
Chelsea: Hatsune Miku?
Kevin: yeah the secret layers are wild what sucks about secret layers um they don't they're they're
Chelsea: Oh, okay, yeah.
Chelsea: Wow, what the heck?
Kevin: limited runs um so basically you have to be there on the release day in the morning at a certain time
Kevin: to to be able to get them or they're gonna sell like concert tickets basically yeah so calvin like
Kevin: had to queue up for that um but uh but yeah no he got it and yeah no it's it's all over the place
Kevin: like I said we probably should do a greenhouse on or on marvel the gathering
Chelsea: Yes. Wow. I'm so out of touch here. I'm looking here like Uncharted, Iron Maiden, Jaws. Oh, Burby. Do a new law. Okay. Wow. Okay. I'm glad. I'm glad I fell off of magic a little bit because I would be bankrupt.
Kevin: Oh, yeah, I forgot about the jokes.
Kevin: That was...
Kevin: Oh, it's bad.
Kevin: It's very, very bad.
Kevin: Like the money and the wild Felix the Cat.
Kevin: That was something.
Kevin: Oh, my gosh.
Kevin: They're doing a dwarf fortress one.
Kevin: That's insane.
Kevin: Who knows?
Kevin: Maybe we'll be able to get a secret lair one day
Kevin: because they're just letting anyone in, I guess.
Chelsea: anyone in here wow no that's neat though I guess um
Kevin: Oh, there's He-Man.
Chelsea: yeah I imagine if they did like a because you know pokemon and magic were both wizards of the
Kevin: I can't.
Chelsea: coast at the start if they did like a pokemon collab with them
Kevin: Okay. Not Pokemon,
Kevin: but there's
Kevin: rumblings. You see
Kevin: Hasbro, the parent company of
Kevin: Wizards of the Coast,
Kevin: you know, from Magic the Gathering.
Chelsea: yeah why are we whispering
Chelsea: we're not
Chelsea: podcasts
Chelsea: we're like come here
Kevin: I don't want to say
Chelsea: tell me your secret
Chelsea: allegedly
Kevin: too loudly because I could
Kevin: be dead wrong, but Hasbro struck a deal.
Chelsea: yes yes I know I can't
Kevin: They're producing toys for
Kevin: Nintendo, specifically Legend of Zelda
Kevin: toys.
Kevin: They look very good. I'm excited
Kevin: for them, but here's
Kevin: the thing. People are thinking,
Kevin: well, the movie's going to be out
Kevin: next year, and there'll
Kevin: be more toys for that, probably, but
Kevin: because it's Hasbro and they own
Kevin: Wizards, we might see
Kevin: Zelda in Magic the Gathering.
Kevin: There's
Kevin: a decent chance, and it's
Kevin: going to be brutal. It's going to be
Kevin: vicious if they do
Kevin: so we might see it
Chelsea: Oh my goodness, I...
Chelsea: Yep.
Chelsea: The minimalism of leaving my body as soon as Zelda is mentioned.
Chelsea: Or Pokemon.
Chelsea: I got room for one more thing on the shelf.
Kevin: yeah so
Kevin: stay tuned listeners for the greenhouse
Kevin: where Chelsea and I
Kevin: talk about
Kevin: as we live play games of
Kevin: the Zelda set of Magic the Gathering
Chelsea: are you a big zelda fan oh good
Kevin: oh yeah
Kevin: we can do a whole greenhouse on that
Kevin: I mean that's appropriate for you for sure
Kevin: I started
Chelsea: you're not a true fan unless you played zelda cdi
Kevin: Wind Waker but I've gone back to a lot
Kevin: Minish Cap
Kevin: I mean I'm Big Toon Link
Kevin: oh okay well you know I am
Chelsea: i'm kidding i'm kidding fake fan
Kevin: a fake fan
Kevin: I played
Chelsea: that's yeah okay you can't you survive that nonsense
Kevin: what's it called
Kevin: Spirit Tracks
Kevin: so that's got me some cred
Kevin: I went through that nonsense
Kevin: ha ha ha
Kevin: yes that's it that's all folks we made it through the news that's a lot of games and updates
Kevin: coming out i'm caught up thank you chelsea do you have anything else you'd like to add
Kevin: to all this or anything you want to share plug et cetera
Chelsea: if you made it this far share your favorite knockoff spirit halloween costume name
Chelsea: because you know how how they have the knockoff names for like I think luigi was green gamer boy
Kevin: Oh, that's a good one.
Chelsea: I think is what the costume box said yesterday so please share your most obscure halloween costume
Chelsea: name find
Kevin: what I want to okay they have to have let's see i'm sorry i'm just checking uh are the because i
Kevin: assume they have the amazing digital circus costume darn it these look official I was hoping for the
Kevin: knockoff names but uh no there they are the the the uh there's the adult palm and jacks there they
Kevin: are um that's good um and dear listener when you find and tell us what knockoff costume you like
Kevin: best you can tell us uh at several of these ths pod
Kevin: uh locations on tumblr at blue sky and blue sky excuse me again that is at ths pod or head down
Kevin: to harvest season.club our bona fide certified website where you can uh message uh al directly
Kevin: about those costumes that you're you you think are good names um that'd be a great one
Chelsea: I want them with no contacts, just all these crazy names and he'll be like, what are you
Kevin: just message him the just the name and see if he can guess what the costume is based on the name
Kevin: oh that's oh that's good you can also see the links for all the show notes and all that good stuff all
Kevin: the episodes on there or if you really want to up your game head on down to patreon.com slash ths pod
Kevin: or where just a small uh just a small uh amount every month you can join in on the fun see the premium
Kevin: Stuff like the slack where we talk
Kevin: About nonsense see all the posted
Kevin: Things Codey dropped out
Kevin: Bugs and things see my thoughts
Kevin: On episodes I'm not on
Kevin: That's that's a thing
Chelsea: I love those live updates.
Kevin: Yeah
Kevin: It's pretty good I there's there's many good
Kevin: Thoughts to many of those episodes
Kevin: It's I
Kevin: I didn't know cicadas did zero rushes
Kevin: That's all I have to say
Kevin: You can also get access
Kevin: To the greenhouse where we have episodes
Kevin: On other topics like the ones we keep talking
Kevin: About we want to make
Kevin: I have many I want to make
Kevin: so we
Kevin: will be coming
Kevin: soon but
Kevin: otherwise
Kevin: thank you for
Kevin: listening dear
Kevin: listeners thank
Kevin: you Chelsea for
Kevin: coming on and
Kevin: joining us on
Kevin: this little journey
Kevin: here and thank
Kevin: you Al for having
Kevin: us and editing and
Kevin: going through all
Kevin: this nonsense yeah
Kevin: and until next
Kevin: time dearest
Kevin: listeners have a
Chelsea: Have a good harvest.
Kevin: good harvest there
Theme Tune: the harvest season is created by al mckinley with support from our patrons including our
Kevin: we go off sync
Kevin: as always
Theme Tune: pro farmers kevin stewart and elisa our art is done by micah the brave and our music is done by
Theme Tune: nick burgess feel free to visit our website harvestseason.club for show notes and links
Theme Tune: to things we discussed in this episode
Kevin: I clapped they say it's recorded but uh i've yet to see evidence to the contrary
Chelsea: I clap too.
Kevin: okay um all right then in that case let's go ahead
Kevin: that's for al sinking and whatnot granted oh no hold on I forget to do the revocal
Kevin: no that's fine you can keep it going let's just okay it's fine just keep it rolling okay
Chelsea: Oh, shoot. Okay, I have mine going. I have mine going.
Chelsea: Okay.
Kevin: 35 in five seconds.
Chelsea: Okay, deal.
Kevin: I clapped okay there we go all right we're good now we're good okay um
Chelsea: Sorry, y'all.